What?
What's the deal with this bear?
Good morning, Boxo.
Oh, wow.
What a surprise.
You don't usually see the director of
the Hunters Association around here.
Hello there.
Ah, you must be the magical tool
everyone keeps going on about.
He really can talk.
A bear in charge of hunters? Mmm.
We're planning to attack
the frog fiends at a nearby
base to lessen the threat
they pose to the village.
Can we count on you and
Boxo for your support?
He didn't mean to include me, did he?
Huh?
Boxo's no good in a fight.
I figured.
But there's nothing more valuable
to hunters on the road than warm,
ready-to-eat food.
Not to mention the supply of
cold drinks for the long marches.
When I said support, I meant it.
And don't worry about Boxxo, I'll
make doubly sure he's well guarded
What do you think, Boxxo?
That sound like something you can do?
I don't really know what's going on,
but it doesn't feel like
something I can ignore.
I want to protect this village and Lamas.
Hello there!
Well, looks like we're in.
Perfect, thanks you two!
This moment is called the.
The time of the song.
You can't stop the drama.
When you face, when you
face, don't stop believing.
When you face, don't stop believing.
When you face, you're just like
Thank you.
It's been three days now
since Lamas and I set out.
Word among the hunters is we're getting
pretty close to the Frog Fiend's base.
According to Director Bear,
the Frog Fiends probably couldn't do
much damage to the village directly,
but they could block its access
to the stratum's transfer circle.
The transfer circle is apparently
some kind of magic device that
connects the Clear Flow Lake stratum
with all the dungeon's other strata,
as well as the surface.
Hey, no way is that them.
There's no doubt about it.
It's that special time
of year again, Shiro.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Pretty sure I am, Aka.
It's the season of money and we're
going to load our pockets with it.
They seem excited.
Munami was saying the frog fiends are such
a hassle because of
their seasonal breeding.
You wake up one morning and
suddenly there are a bunch of them.
Did you hear?
Apparently there are way more frog fiends
this year than a usual breeding season.
Oh, really?
It shouldn't be a problem.
I mean, look at this team.
Hmm.
You don't have to be so tense
you know it's like director
bear promised you've got
plenty of muscle guarding
you so there's no need to
worry right this is the
magic endless food box right
this thing's got quite a
reputation in the village
his name's box oh and if you
put some coins in him you
can buy anything you see in
the window no way that's
convenient I can't exactly
walk away from something like
this without trying it out
let's see oh I think I'm
gonna try this one with a
picture that looks like a
sliced lomawa thank you very
much you talk oh man this
is weird I gotta say though
I'm impressed never had an
experience quite like this
this is an incredibly detailed
picture too there's no
way somebody did all this
on their own come to think
of it I've never looked at
the pictures that much it's
kind of hard when the empty
containers disappear oh?
Oh, don't worry about
the trash, by the way.
You serious?
Well, I gotta see that.
That's good!
That's really good!
And it's warm, too.
That's so awesome.
I'm gonna drink a lot of these,
so make sure you stock up, okay?
Actually, as far as I can tell, we
don't have to do any restocking.
We buy and we buy, but he never runs dry.
Pretty weird, huh?
Interesting.
I think I might know someone
else who'd like to meet you.
Hey, Filmina, you gotta come see this.
Well, here I am.
What is it, Captain Kerioyl?
You're telling me Stubble
is the leader of the guards?
I had the wrong read on this guy.
He must be serious. Okay, Filmina,
I want you to use all your knowledge
about ancient treasures and
magic tools to unlock the mysteries
of this wonderful little box.
There don't appear to be any mysteries.
There's nothing magic about this thing.
It's just a block of iron.
Well, yeah.
I'm a vending machine.
I've never met any other
block of iron that can
sell you a warm drink
from an endless supply.
What do you think it's keeping this stuff?
Another dimension?
Potentially.
But an effect like that would have to be
the result of quite an unusual blessing.
And I can't imagine a blessing would
work on something without a soul,
such as this box.
Oh, man.
I wish I could tell them how wrong she is.
According to my magic
expert, you are very strange.
Doesn't trouble me.
As long as you're here
to help, I could use you.
So thanks, Boxo.
We're real glad to have you here.
Thank you very much.
All right, everyone.
You are relieved for the night.
Prepare yourselves for tomorrow.
Now's my chance to earn
some repeat business.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.
I had to thank the hunters
for earning me so many points.
So I added a new function.
So good.
I feel the chill in my bones
melting away with every bite.
I don't know what this meat is,
but I can't get enough of it.
Nights and mornings are
getting pretty cold these days.
and nothing farts a
chill like cup noodles.
It tastes so good!
Every flavor I've had has been incredible.
I can't wait to try the rest of them.
I'm pretty sure that
girl's one of the guards.
She eats a lot for someone so small.
Your stomach's like a
bottomless pit, I'm impressed.
Oh, I'm just getting started, trust me.
I almost forgot to introduce myself, I'm
Lamas. Right. Good to meet you. I'm Shiro.
May I join you?
Oh, Director.
I wanted to talk with you about tomorrow.
We've got about three hours
of marching in the morning,
but after that, we'll launch
our attack on the Frog Fiends.
I brought you along to provide food.
Any other decisions are yours to make.
That said, would you prefer to wait
here or join us on the battlefield?
You know, Boxo's not a hunter.
I am so normally I wouldn't mind it's
just I really don't think he wants me to.
Drag him out there too bad are you
telling me you want me to drag you out?
There hello there well that settles
it director it looks like box so and
me will Be joining you on the
battlefield I knew I could count on you.
I'm stronger than you think, Lamas.
You're my first customer
and my first friend.
I promise I'm going to protect you.
The air's like a dog's mouth.
And the ground's all muddy, too.
It's really hard to walk in this.
We're right on top of them! Attack!
Ready when you are!
All right, then, let's do it!
Let's stack some bodies, people!
The bigger the pile of rocks,
the bigger the pile of gold!
You did it!
It's our time to shine,
Boxo, are you ready?
Hello there!
Wait a minute, didn't Lana say
she's really bad at landing hits?
How's this gonna work?
Yeah!
Wait, I actually hit it?
Oh, man, I hit it good, too!
It looks like the extra weight
on her back is balancing her.
Could it be we make the perfect team?
I'm pretty sure I figured
out what happened.
Thanks, Boxo. Hello there.
I'm so happy to help.
Although I never would have guessed
this was one of my functions.
Rise, water.
Take shape to my will and pierce them.
Something's off about this.
There's no way there should
be this many of them.
It's starting to look
like the rumors were true.
Shuckle up, everybody.
Things are getting serious, so
pick someone and watch their back.
This is bad.
What are we going to do?
So which is it?
Was this your bad
planning or your bad luck?
We can whine later.
If it starts to feel like we're
gonna lose, we can ditch the wagon.
I'm not giving up just yet!
Hey, thanks for looking out!
I don't sweat it, it was easy enough.
Oh no!
Stay away from her!
Whoa, what's up with this light?
I didn't know you could do that.
I can't.
I'm not gonna complain about it, but it
would be nice to know how it's happening.
That was close.
I'd better revisit the function
that widens my field of view.
There it is!
A thousand points seemed so expensive
when I was sitting at the end.
What a difference!
I can see everything at once now.
Voxo, keep an eye out for
enemies back there, okay?
You could even win a reward. Sounds good.
If you say that, there's an enemy coming.
Now let's get out there
and turn this around.
Hello there.
You've got quite a punch.
I've never seen someone lay
out a frog being barehanded.
It's pretty impressive.
Captain, don't say that,
I'm really nothing special.
You can win a reward!
Boxxo, I thought you'd say how
big is it's everywhere for you!
I'm trying to tell you about the enemies!
Forget about the punching,
how'd you do this?
A blessing of the Earth?
The same thing happened a second ago.
I think Baxo's doing it.
Baxo's doing it? Well, well.
I've never seen anybody so
obviously up to no good.
Time to upgrade him to
potentially dangerous.
Boxxo, I think you and I are
going to be real good friends.
I'm sorry, Stubble, but
your request is denied.
Take that!
It was dicey for a minute,
but we still got the job done.
Remember to cut those
tongues off, everybody.
We'll turn them in at
the association later.
You're welcome to join us if you'd like.
What's the matter, Captain?
Afraid of getting your hands dirty?
Are you kidding me?
the main reason i took this job was so i
could make you guys do
that stuff you tyrant no
fair you don't pay us enough you got some
serious guts talking to
your captain that way
these guys seem really
comfortable with each other
so filmina what do you
think our next move is we
got a pretty good haul
today but it could be better
we could get a lot more
gold if we went to the
front lines to get more
tongues i understand what
you're trying to say but
we were given a job to do
and that's guarding llamas
and boxo i know but come
on vice captain you know
as well as i do we need
funds to run the group
and this is the best way
i was gonna give you all
a bonus if we pulled it
off too oh what a shame
truly such a shame have
it your way captain we can
go to the front lines if
you want but we're not
going to do this unless
llamas and boxo agree to
it obviously what kind of
monster do you think i am
you keep on worrying this
much and your wrinkles are
going to get even worse.
Try taking it easy once in a while.
Vice-Captain Phil Mina,
feel free to take a swing at him.
On that note, would you like to
come to the front lines with us?
Come on, let's go.
Don't you want to go?
It'll be so much fun on the front lines.
I've seen what you can do.
I know you want to fight them, so...
I want to help.
If you think Boxxo and I can be of use
there, then I know what my decision is.
Let's get there before
someone else is all the fun.
You okay with that, Boxo?
Hello there.
That takes care of that.
We've got to get all these
injured people into the wagon.
You're going to be okay. Thank you.
I feel bad.
These guys got hurt
fighting for the village.
Is there something I can do?
I know!
Hey, check it out!
You could even win a reward!
You want me to pass these items
out to the wounded hunters?
Hello there!
At the very least, I
can keep them hydrated.
Feel free to drink as
much as you like, okay?
Thanks.
I really appreciate it.
Yeah, you're a lifesaver.
That was nice of you, Boxo.
Thank you very much!
Thanks for the assistance, Kerioyl.
Just the kind of work I expect
from the Menagerie of Fools.
Menagerie of Fools?
That's a weird name for a group.
We had a little time on our hands, but
you could have gotten by without us.
It's true, we would have won the day.
Though your cooperation is
appreciated all the same.
Can you think of a reason
we were confronted with
so many more frog fiends
than we expected to face?
I've only got one guess, and I
don't think you're going to like it.
Are you guys having some
secret meeting, or...?
You're still speculating,
but evidence is beginning to mount that a
King Frog Fiend was born
this breeding season.
A King Frog Fiend?
Sounds scary.
I really hope we don't
come across that thing.
I hired your team to act as
bodyguards for Lamas and Boxo,
but if we really are dealing
with a King Frog Fiend,
that changes things drastically.
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to ask for your help. Sure.
A nasty job like this is just
perfect for the Menagerie of Fools.
Hmm.
We'll need food.
Can I count on the two of you for that?
Are you and Boxxo
willing to keep the group
supplied while we search
for the King Frog Fiend?
That's what Boxxo and I do best.
Hey, anyone available to
give me a hand over here?
Yeah, I'll be right there. Bye.
I gotta leave you alone for a little
while, but don't you cry while I'm gone.
I look forward to serving you again.
Okay,
fine, don't miss me, but I'm going to
remember this the next time you're lonely.
That was the kind of conversation a
flesh-and-blood person would have with a lover.
Sadly, I am but a vending machine.
Finally alone.
Whoa, who's this guy?
Hey, hey, hey, are you
trying to steal my money?
Hello there.
Listen, if you don't stop making noise,
I'm going to destroy you, got it?
Ah, that's right.
Keep them coming, you freak of nature.
Why is this so damn hot? Ha-ha-ha!
How about some extra hot corn
soup for my favorite customer?
You!
You dumb-ass box!
You just made your last mistake!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm sorry, am I interrupting something?
Wait, please, let me explain!
Don't cause any more trouble
you reap what you sow jerk
It's the King Throat Pete what
the hell's it doing over here?
I don't know but it looks pissed off
You're right, Boxo.
I need to calm down.
Okay, let's get you out of here.
Shit, I can't get the Unasusu to go!
We've got to find a way to
get this wagon moving now!
It's coming!
Hey, it'll all be okay.
Mm-hmm.
I thought she was going to do that.
What do you think you're doing?
Why did you cut them loose?
Cause I'm not too scared to pull!
Are you serious? We're moving!
Okay, what do I do?
I could probably protect Lamas with her
barrier, but I can't cover the whole wagon.
No!
She'd never forgive me if I
saved her and let the others die.
I need another idea!
Do I have anything in my inventory
I can use to slow it down?
Come on, there's got to be
something I can do here!
Damn it! Something! Anything!
Wait a minute.
Oh, that's perfect!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for what?
Oh, wait, are you saying you
have something that can help?
Hello there!
I knew you'd come up with a plan!
I don't understand, but
it's better than nothing!
Now I just gotta buy a new function.
Form change!
Whoa, Voxo, you got all
roundy! Wait a minute.
Why hasn't she complimented
any of my other forms?
Okay, so, uh, this thing fits
into the plan somehow, right?
Here's the hard part.
How am I going to
communicate what she needs to
do with everything now that
she has all the pieces?
Please insert coins.
What?
You want me to pay you right now?
We don't really have time for that.
Too bad.
Please insert coins.
Please insert coins. I...
I don't understand.
I'm so sorry, but I don't
know what else to do.
This is too much for a vending
machine to communicate.
We gotta move.
I think this thing is just busted.
Don't say that.
He's trying to tell me something.
And whatever it is, I know it's important!
She's putting so much faith in me,
but there's nothing more I can do!
Please, Lamas, give up
on the plan and run!
So I take these things and
then do something with coins?
Is that it?
What the hell did I just wake up to?
You guys gotta untie me!
There's no way I'm
gonna die here with you!
Hurry! Shut up!
I'm sorry, you idiot, I'm a good
place of water, hurry, hurry!
Drink this and calm down.
I think that's it.
What the hell?
What kind of drink explodes?
It hurts my eyes!
They got it!
This is a well-known
phenomenon where I come from,
but it's completely unknown to them.
If you put a certain minty candy into
cola, the results are shocking to behold.
I get it.
We just have to put this
candy into this drink.
Hello there.
You heard him, everyone.
You guys ready?
Yeah, let's do it!
Now aim for the eyes and fire!
What in the world's going on here?
Hurry, everyone.
We need to help Blomas and Boxxo.
Already honored.
Ah!
All right, it's finally over!
Thanks, Boxo.
We owe it all to you, buddy.
I look forward to serving you again.
Lamas, when we couldn't find
the wagon at the meeting point,
we were scared to death.
I know, Director. I'm sorry.
Your actions kept those
hunters alive and safe.
I would never ask you
to apologize for that.
The fault is mine.
But if I had just stayed where you told us
to, then you would have found us easier.
I'm so sorry.
The girl and the bear began to
take turns bowing to each other.
It was a surreal yet
strangely heartwarming sight.
Mission accomplished, everybody.
Let's go home.
But until we reach the village,
this is still an organized march.
Stay on your toes.
Yes, sir!
I'll see
you
next time
If you like me, I'll tell
you when I'm going to come.
When the dawn's early,
let's go to sleep with you.
As long as you can see,
we'll have a good dream.
and look forward to serving you again.